Guide to the The Women's Sports Foundation Records 1974-2019 MS 3199
New-York Historical Society
Women's Sports Foundation records
circa 1970s-2019
New-York Historical Society
Women's Sports Foundation
MS 3199
660 Linear feet in 659 record cartons
TBD
Arrangement
TBD
Biographical / Historical
TBD
Access Restrictions
MSS: Open to qualified researchers.
PPAC: Open to qualified researchers by appointment only. To schedule an appointment, contact the Print Room Librarian at printroom@nyhistory.org.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
TBD
Scope and Contents
TBD
- Series I. Women's Sports Foundation archives
  - Subseries I.A. Chronological files
    - Women's Sports subscription offer, 1974 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - Philosophy and statement of purpose, 1974 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - WomenSports subscriber survey, 1974 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - College scholarship guide, 1975 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action program, 1975 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - Seminars, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      Scope and Contents
      Contains Frontiers newsletter, Volume 1 number 1, 2, and 3.
    - Film proposal The Importance of Sports, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
    - Promotional, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
    - College scholarship guide, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
    - Revlon Sports Skills, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
    - Revlon Physical Conditioning Guide, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
    - Revlon Publicity and Promotions Handbook, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 13)
    - Revlon Sport Organization Guide, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 14)
    - Revlon Title IX Guide, 1976 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter, 1977 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 16)
    - Women in Motion, 1977 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 17)
    - Misc. proposals, 1977 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 18)
    - Running certification project, 1977 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
    - College scholarship guide, 1977 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 20)
    - Camp scholarship program, 1977 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 21)
    - Wade trophy, 1978 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 22)
    - Challenge and choice dinners, 1978 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 23)
    - Newsletter, 1978 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 24)
    - The All-Star Salute to Women's Sports, 1978 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 25)
    - Women's Sport posters [proposal], 1978 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 26)
    - Women's athletic club proposal, 1978 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 27)
    - Camp scholarship program (Offsite-box 1, Folder 28)
    - Dance-A-Thon, 1978 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 29)
    - Women's Sports magazine promotion, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 30)
    - Newsletter, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 31)
    - Amateur sports club proposal, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 32)
    - Associate WSF New York, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 33)
    - Associate WSF New York/ Westchester, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 34)
    - Associate WSF New Jersey, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 35)
    - Associate WSF New England, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 36)
    - Associate WSF Northwest, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 37)
    - Associate WSF St. Louis, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 38)
    - Membership promotion, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 39)
    - Associations summaries, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 40)
    - Association leaders and letters, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 41)
    - College scholarship guide, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 42)
    - Wade trophy dinner, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 43)
    - Camp scholarship program, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 44)
    - Title IX President Carter, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 45)
    - Quarterly reports, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 46)
    - High school all star award, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 47)
    - Get into condition program, 1979 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 48)
    - Quarterly report, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
    - [Poster proposals], 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
    - Film proposal, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
    - Camp scholarship program, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
    - College scholarship guide, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
    - [Grodins All Women's Run], 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
    - New York Dinner, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
    - Women's Sports subscriber survey, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
    - Third annual Margaret Wade awards dinner, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 9)
    - Women's sport expo, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10)
    - Publicity proposal, 1980 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 11)
    - Camp scholarship program, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 12)
    - College scholarship guide, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
    - Toyota Championships, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
    - Quarterly report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
    - [Sportsline], 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 16)
    - Women's sports conference, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 17)
    - Nominating committee correspondence, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 18)
    - Newsletter, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
    - Awards program, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 20)
    - NYAD, 1981 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 21)
    - Dinner (New York), 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 22)
    - Camp scholarship program, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 23)
    - Annual report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 24)
    - Proposal WSF national education and resource center, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 25)
    - College scholarship guide, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
    - Nominating committee correspondence, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 27)
    - Newsletter, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 28)
    - Baseball reunion, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 29)
    - Peanuts poster, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 30)
    - Project MAP, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 31)
    - Women's fitness sports med., 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 32)
    - Women's Sports Hall of Fame, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 33)
    - Coca Cola media tour, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 34)
    - National fitness classic, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 35)
    - Marketing proposal - Jill Wing, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 36)
    - Tennis proposals, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 37)
    - Women's sports clinics, 1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 38)
    - New agenda conference, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 39)
    - Selection ballot - individual contribution, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 40)
    - Newsletter, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 41)
    - Awards, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 42)
    - Drummond estate, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 43)
    - Camp scholarship program, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 44)
    - California raisin advisory board, 1983 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 45)
    - Himalayan expedition, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
    - Ocean Spray, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
    - College scholarship guide, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
    - Nightline women in sports, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
    - Publicity and promotion handbook, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
    - Over 30's tennis classic, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
    - Careers guide, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
    - Women's fitness/ sports med., 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
    - Special programs, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9)
    - National fitness clinic, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
    - New agenda, 1983 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
    - The graphic art of Charles Schulz, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
    - E. Auchincloss speech re: effectiveness Title IX, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 13)
    - Olympics promotion, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 14)
    - Women's fitness and health program, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 15)
    - High school all-star winners, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 16)
    - Women's sports hall of fame, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 17)
    - Camp scholarship program, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 18)
    - College scholarship guide, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 19)
    - Awards program, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 20)
    - Annual report, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 21)
    - Associate British WSF, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 22)
    - Newsletter, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 23)
    - Personal products, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 24)
    - The role and place of sport and fitness in the lives of American women: a scientific study, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 25)
    - Tribute to Esther Williams, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 26)
    - Hogathon, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 27)
    - Women's fitness invitational, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 28)
    - Women's marathon celebration, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 29)
    - Women in motion, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 30)
    - Fund raising campaign, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 31)
    - Athletic games with California beef council, 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 32)
    - Aspire higher, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 33)
    - An evening of achievement, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 34)
    - New York dinner, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 35)
    - High school all-star winners, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 36)
    - College scholarship guide, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 37)
    - Camp guide/ scholarships, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 38)
    - CA beef council, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 39)
    - Car council, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 40)
    - Coupon ads, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 41)
    - Publicity NYAP, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 42)
    - The financial district strut, 1985 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
    - Women's sports and fitness, 1985 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
    - Resource materials, 1985 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
    - Newsletter, 1985 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
    - Revlon award, 1985 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
    - Annual report, 1985 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
    - Miller Lite report, 1985 December (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    - The greatest American athlete of the last 25 years, 1985 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    - Awards program production, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9)
    - Speaker's bureau, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 10)
    - The strength within: health and fitness, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
    - Women's sports alliance Marin City, California, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
    - Public relations/ marketing, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
    - Awards program, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 14)
    - Headway newsletter, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 15)
    - A salute to women in sports, 1986 September (Offsite-box 4, Folder 16)
    - Book/ video club, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 17)
    - Strategies for success, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 18)
    - Internship program, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 19)
    - New agenda, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 20)
    - New York dinner, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 21)
    - Levi Strauss contribution award, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 22)
    - Milky way high school all-star awards, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 23)
    - Women's sports and fitness qualitative research study, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 24)
    - Ocean Spray, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 25)
    - Scholarship guide, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 26)
    - Women's sports hall of fame, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 27)
    - Up and coming award winners, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 28)
    - CAR (Coachs' Advisory Round table), 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 29)
    - Travel and training fund, 1986 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 30)
    - New agenda, 1987 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 31)
  - Subseries I.B. Publications archive